[Music]
[Música]
yes
sí
for the same
por las mismas
[Music] yes yes yes
[Música]
[Music]
[Música]
the many things
las muchas cosas
yes
sí
[Music]
[Música]
then
entonces
is not my
es mi
case to follow
caso el de seguir
the track I'm going dealers
la pista me voy dealers
the little
el pequeño
[Music]
[Música]
place
place
tension
tensión
[Music]
[Música]
to walk
a andar
my body
mi cuerpo
at the level it is now
en el nivel que está ahora
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
no
no
[Music]
[Música]
is
está
how
cómo
[Music]
[Música]
in this aspect
en este aspecto
for me
para mí
yes me baby forget me it's place in the
sí me baby olvídame es place en la
champions
champions
[Music]
[Música]
at home which is essential
en casa que es esencial
next to me
junto a mí
[Music] it
[Música]
's
es
good to know that there is one no no
bueno saber que allí está uno
no
no no
for everyone
para todos
and
i
no
no
when I was well
cuando estaba bien
we talked
nos hablamos
[Music]
[Música]
well
bien
afp
afp
[Music]
[Música]
end
fin
[Music]
[Música]
and
y
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
the store
la tienda
and so or the archangel Maria Maria Ignacia
y así o el arcángel maría maría ignacia
Maria Ignacia but it almost burned
maría ignacia pero que casi se quema
real scare it doesn't really scare
susto de verdad que no asusta de verdad
the archangel of windy Maria Ignacia thank you
el arcángel de windy maría ignacia mucha
very much queen thank you very much
gracia a reina muchísimas gracias
sweetheart what a good way to start
corazón que bueno una manera de empezar
the live
el directo
doku thanks to you too for doing for
doku gracias a ti también por hacerte
throwing the pse prime what a good way
por tirar el pse prime que buena manera
to start the live and I'm going to know how to
de empezar el directo y te voy a saber
wait for there to be more people so that
esperar que hubiera más gente para que
more people could see it honey but
más gente lo viera cariño pero
thank you very much Maria Ignacia I'm going to
muchísimas gracias maría ignacia voy a
leave the handsome finished you this is
dejar el guapo acabados ustedes esto es
I'm not for this the three for
yo no estoy para esto los tres para
these attacks these attack this mini
estos ataques éstos ataque este minis
heart attack demanded okay but well
infarto demandaba vale pero bueno ya
the link for the members on
está fijado el enlace de los miembros en
YouTube is already set okay so that whoever wants to
youtube vale para que quien quiera
become a member becomes a double member
hacerse miembro se haga miembro doble
how many members are we see it like this
cuantos miembros somos lo ve así
we still have to recover the least
todavía nos queda por recuperar lo menos
that we are going to recover let's see it's very
que vamos recuperar a ver es muy
early I know there will be very few people
temprano sé que va a haber poquita gente
abi I gave you 100  100 bucks for the
abi te dio 100 pavos 100 pavos para el
for life' I
for life'
already know it's gone 12 marinas already in our
ya lo sé se vaya 12 marinas ya en el
hearts we carry you in our hearts we
corazón te llevamos en el corazón te
carry you marinas now thank you very much for
llevamos marinas ya muchas gracias por
those beats
esos beats
thank you very much for those beeps
muchas gracias por esos bip
[Music]
[Música]
early time you almost killed grandpa
tiempo temprano casi matas al abuelo
totally I swear I have like a
totalmente os lo juro que tengo como una
small projection of air here between my
pequeña proyección de aire aquí entre el
chest and my back
pecho y la espalda
[ __ ] let me know it became official today
ostias avisa se hizo oficial hoy día
work mind with my accent with my speech
trabaja mente con mi acento con mi habla
with my [ __ ] in my mouth it seems I
con mi [__] en la boca que parece que
have how are things going do it through the
tengo cómo va la cosa hazlo a través del
link that was just posted okay if
enlace que acaba de poner vale si
listen me the members are missing a lot to
escucha me los miembros faltan mucho por
recover whoever can become a member we don't
recuperar quien pueda hacerse miembro no
want any upset like what
queremos disgusto como lo que le ha
happened to albert okay whoever can become a
pasado a albert vale quien pueda hacerse
member the link is pinned in the chat
miembro el enlace está fijado en el chat
okay whoever is tweeting and wants to throw away
vale quienes estén tweets y quiera tirar
amazon prime okay if you have amazon
el amazon prime vale si teneis amazon
prime put it on and leave it to me don't
prime ponle dar y me lo dejáis a mí no
leave it to him this money
se lo dejéis este dinero que se lo queda
someone will keep it in prison because it's so early
alguien preso porque es tan temprano
because I'm going to go to the beach now to
porque me voy a ir a la playa ahora a
take a walk and eat what's going on I can I can't it doesn't
darme una vuelta ya comer que pasa puedo
matter that it's early I know  that
da igual que sea temprano sé que
made things worse for the people then
agravaba lo de la gente después no pasa
nothing happens either there is not much issue there are two or
nada tampoco hay mucho tema hay dos o
three issues that I wanted to
tres temita que quería que quería
comment on there are two or three issues I did not want to
comentar hay dos o tres temita no quería
comment on the video not even the
comentar el vídeo ni siquiera los
issues of the lights I have to take the dog
cuestiones de las luces al perro lo
down too before leaving so
tengo que bajar también antes de irme o
we're going to be quick it looks a
sea que vamos a estar rápido se ve un
bit 2019 made in 2018 when we
poco 2019 hecho de 2018 cuando lo
had it good do you remember before I didn't
teníamos bien os acordáis yo antes no
put airplane you
ponía avión vos
before I had the camera like more like this
yo ante tener la cámara como más así
the TV could be seen and I would turn the TV a little
se veía la tele y giraba un poco la tele
and on the TV I would put more or less the things that we
y en la tele ponía más o menos las cosas
are talking about base how I have
de las que estamos hablando base cómo he
been adding things to the furniture you know well
ido añadiendo cosas en el mueble sabes
each time I am putting the camera more
pues cada vez voy echando la cámara más
towards this so that the furniture can be seen more
para acá para que se vaya viendo más el
and I will end up like this well
mueble y acabaré
because we are leaving today you have
así bueno porque ya nos vamos hoy me
seen me there the yogurt what things not like
habéis visto ahí el yogur vaya cosas no
listening to me two skinny girls two little
en plan escucharme dos flaquitas dos
plates let's go for the third okay on
plaquitas vamos a por la tercera vale en
TVs to the CEO on TVs to the CEO what's going on you are not
teles al ceo en teles al ceo que pasa no
helping the lordship hd is
ayudáis a la señoría hd
not helping that one the signal hurt the
no ayuda a esa la señal herí a las
lordships help the ugt
señorías ayuda a ugt
the lordships  help you always
las señorías ayuda siempre a usted
looked good on TV well I'm not
se veía bien lo de la tele pues no lo
going to put it more than good I'm
voy a poner más que bien
not going to put it more than good
no lo voy a poner más que bien
I'm a member not incarnate you are not a
soy una miembro no encarna no eres
member at home you are not a member it does not come out that
miembro en casa no eres miembro no sale
being ours what was said family
que ser nuestro lo dicho familia
subscribe tie them to the CEO we are going to
suscribiros áteles al ceo vamos a
help the people of the lordship so that we
ayudarle a la gente de la señoría que
reach 100,000 and have three
lleguemos a los 100.000 y tengamos tres
plates in the new studio I am going to put
placas en el estudio nuevo voy a poner
three plates the plate plate appears to me to
tres placas la placa placa me aparece al
Carlos Jean or writing it directly from
carlos jean o escribiéndolo directa de
three to the CEO okay
tres al ceo vale
today direct TV salseros well I don't believe
hoy directo tele salseros pues no creo
its end I don't think it will come in time I am your
su fin no creo que llegue a tiempo estoy
lordship and also kids
señoría y también chavalería
united for a cause magaly united for
unidos por una causa magaly unidos por
the cause
la causa
if you still have the refrigerator with the bar
si tienes todavía la nevera con el bar
inside I have the rod and the place is
adentro tengo el vara y el lugar está
there in that glass look at this yellow thing
ahí en ese cristal mira esto amarillo
that you see on the glass stuck on that
que veis en el cristal pegado por aquel
side the bar I have the refrigerator
lado el bar la nevera la tengo guardada
in it I have the refrigerator yes
en él la tengo guardada la nevera sí
but I don't know if I will put it in the
pero no sé si la pondré en el estudio
new studio but in sight it is a little old it
nuevo pero a la vista está un poco vieja
is a little old do you remember that
ya está un poco vieja os acordáis que
and this reminds me there is a clearing because we do
y esto me recuerda hay un claro porque
not have  old people when I don't
no tenemos viejos cuando lo de yo no
CC
cc
listen to me do you remember that I told you the
escúchame os acordáis que os dije el
other day that there was success communicates
otro día que había el éxito comunica el
Sevilla look here is the proof good
sevilla mira aquí está la prueba buena
proof that he came but well if yes yes yes yes yes I don't
prueba de que lo vino pero bueno si lo
know if that same day is
sí sí sí sí no sé si ese mismo día esté
because I think that with these clothes it wouldn't go I
porque creo que con esta ropa no iba
think that with those clothes we would get along well I
creo que con esa ropa nos llevaría bien
swear
os lo juro
sometimes to the area in front of this uncle
a veces a la zona ante el tío de este
Paco from Paco's men witnesses
paco el de los hombres de paco' testigos
of a friend of mine
de un amigo mío
is the uncle of a friend of mine the subtle one let's go
es tío de un amigo mío el sutil vamos
Paco Tous Paco Tous having put the
paco tous paco tous haber puesto el
famous one who appears in the money heist and
famoso al que sale la casa de papel y
that and the men but above all the one from
eso y los hombres pero sobre todo el de
Paco's men
los hombres de paco'
but he is the uncle of my friend the
pero es el tío de mi amigo el
east let's see I saw him in the Plaa Espanya
este a ver yo lo vi por la plaça espanya
here he is in the center here is the
aquí está en el centro aquí está la
cathedral
catedral
this I think is not the same day
esto yo creo que no es el mismo día
for what exposed in a photo of yesterday and
para que expuesta en una foto de ayer y
today yesterday
hoy ayer
1969 this little boy of five years and today is
1969 este niñito de cinco años y hoy es
the same today operating here in the back there
el mismo hoy por hoy operando aquí atrás
is an area to have a little wine not to
hay una zona para tomar el vinito no
have a tapa the ham look it is  like
tomarla la tapita el jamón vean es como
an old mansion the hams hanging
una casona antigua los jamones colgando
a bit of this Sevillian culture that you
un poco de esta cultura sevillana que se
breathe which is very classic it's just what
respira que es bien clásica es justo lo
one imagines in Spain when you
que uno se imagina en españa cuando
hear I'm going from Spain it's the
escuchas voy de españa es son los
scenes that you imagine
escenarios que te imaginas
well you would
bueno
see that dying well Sevilla Betis and
se vería que morir bueno sevilla betis y
above all what I see is that it consumes a lot
sobre todo lo que veo es que gasta mucho
look here in Nervin Plaza I live close
mira aquí en nervión plaza yo vivo cerca
right now I still live close to
ahora mismo todavía yo vivo cerca de
this
esto
live at the Sevilla field well
en directo en el campo del sevilla pues
the stadiums stop a lot days
se para mucho en los estadios días
the stadiums stop a lot I don't know why
se para muchos los estadios no sé por
for it to record I imagine they would have
para que grabe me imagino que tendrían
some kind of permission requested beforehand or whatever
un tipo de permiso pedido antes o lo que
the Swiss one is to miss you it was quite
sea el helvético perderme ti estaba bien
far from where I live no
lejitos de donde yo vivo no
these are the clothes I was wearing when I
esta es la ropa que llevaba cuando yo lo
saw it I think
vi creo
those are the clothes I was wearing when I
esa es la ropa que llevaba cuando yo lo
saw it but it hasn't been recorded from Ovid I
vi pero no lo ha grabado del ovidio lo
saw it in Plaza Espaa it is recorded from the
vi en la plaza españa está grabado de
lobby
lobby
orange city ham and football
ciudad de naranja jamón y fútbol
her the orange city soap and
ella la ciudad de naranjas jabón y
football let's
fútbol
watch this match it's okay Sevilla
a ver este partido es vale sevilla
not yet
todavía no
the derby anything is worth it and it really doesn't
el derby vale de todo y de verdad no
matter that they are better there's El Corte
importa que sean mejores está el corte
Ingls  Nervin if I'm not mistaken of
inglés de nervión si no me equivoco
course friends all my life all the time
claro amigos toda la vida todo el tiempo
the day of the match the day of the big derby
el día del partido el día del gran derbi
rivals friendly rivalry what's
rivales rivalidad amistosa lo que está
happening behind me
pasando atrás de mí
is the cut of Luis Montoto
es el corte de luis montoto
and here the Meli Hotel very close to
y aquí el hotel meliá muy cerca de
this excitement in the Plaza Espanya I saw it I
esta emoción en la plaza espanya lo vi
continue here someone I know and look up
sigo por aquí alguien conocido y vean
there or rather sizes
hasta allá o sea tallas
it fills it
lo llena
imagine that I see my father what is he doing here
imagina que veo a mi padre que hace aquí
dad we are right now with the
papá nos estamos ahora mismo con los
states of great here he is then
estados de gran aquí que está entonces
walk
anda
from the match really
desde el partido de verdad
active to the people throwing the lid to
activo hasta la gente echando la tapa a
several of these are the streets
varias de estas son las calles por
behind I worked in a shoe store that is
detrás yo trabajé en una zapatería que
here these are the streets behind
hay aquí estas son las calles por detrás
the Nervin Plaza
del nervión plaza
and I
y
know it is in the mural is outside the
tenga que es en el mural está afuera del
stadium he is there he is immortalized
estadio él está ahí está inmortalizado
for all time no no that I no not even
por todos los tiempos no no que yo no ni
nostalgia no to talk a little with the
nostalgia no platicar un ratito con el
man it is lived like a different thing from
hombre se vive como una cosa distinta de
Seville a very football city I think
sevilla una ciudad muy futbolera yo creo
that the most humor is the field Sevilla is that it
que la más humor el campo el sevilla es
supports it I mean the Sevilla field
que le apoya o sea el campo del sevilla
is incredibly beautiful I did not say anything to him
es increíblemente guapo no le dije nada
because I was with the child  the child was
porque yo iba con el niño el niño se me
leaving for the pigeons I didn't have him close I did
iba para las palomas no lo tenía cerca
n't have him close I couldn't have him I would have
no lo tenía cerca no lo pude lo hubiera
greeted him let's see he would have greeted me
saludado a ver me hubiera saludado
if he had been closer the
si hubiera tenía más cerca la vida
healthy life said is what we do
saludable dicho es lo que hacemos
video
videíto
meeting lucas ocampo
conociendo a lucas ocampo
but these are several days in which this this that
pero estos son varios días en el que
the sun is recording
esto esto que está grabando el sol
I arrived at that several days
yo llegué a que varios días
because I wanted that I saw him I went like this I do
porque quería que yo lo vi iba como así
n't know but I saw him in the plaza espanya
no sé pero yo lo vi en la plaza espanya
and at the moment national the plaza espanya
y de momento nacional la plaça espanya
in fact I have photos of that day okay
de hecho yo tengo fotos de ese día vale
decrees photos that day that the photos are these
decretos fotos ese día que las fotos son
these and you know what it is that I
estas y sabéis qué es lo que hacía el
realized because I had
que me di cuenta yo porque yo había
look at it that's what he did was that after a while
mírala es lo que hacía era que al rato
he was uploading
ya él iba subiendo
stories dictated but later for
historias dictara pero más tarde sea por
example now I go down the street I recorded
ejemplo yo ahora voy por la calle grabó
a story distar okay and I upload it after a
una historia distará vale y la subo al
while you
rato
understand the v after a while I didn't have them
me entendéis las v al rato no las tuve
at the moment the story is not
en el momento la historia no es en
live he uploads it like after 3 hours
directo la sube como a las 3 horas
so that people don't go to where he
para que la gente no lo vaya a donde él
is I imagine but anyway family
esté me imagino pero bueno familia
how are you how are you  you are today I'm going to
qué tal estáis qué tal estáis hoy voy a
talk about a couple of I want to react to
hablar de un par de quiero reaccionar a
Angelica's videos but I don't have
los vídeos de angélica pero no me da
time the 7 at least that
tiempo las 7 menos que
all those abi do - I'm not
lo hacen todos esos abi - yo no me
going to bed from now on from
acuesto a partir de ahora a partir de
now on I do it right she was going to thank you very much
ahora lo hago bien se iba muchas gracias
for becoming a member welcome friends
por hacerte miembro bienvenido amigos
welcome remind you all well 3
bienvenidos recordaros a todos bueno 3
cms and they go 3 m / s leonas or white
cms y van 3 m/s leonas o blanco
reminding you all that we leave the
recordando a todos que dejamos fijado el
link fixed by the members and nothing and that if you
enlace por los miembros y nada y que si
are in tweets and you have Amazon Prime
estáis en tweets y tenéis amazon prime
then also leave the Prime there
pues que dejéis también el prime por ahí
for tweets okay I'm going to be there for a little while
por tweets vale voy a estar poco tiempo
I would like to see a video of Angela if it does
me gustaría ver un vídeo de ángela se
n't work for them but I won't have time
les no va pero no me va a dar tiempo
then I'm going to talk about a couple of
pues entonces voy a hablar de un par de
salt I know you have here
sal se os que tengo aquí
to upload them who knows little guy and if we don't have
para subirlos a saber canijo y si no nos
time then go at night look
da tiempo pues ya ve por la noche mira
now so as not to on a Sunday so that he already
ya para que no un domingo para que ya
works beyond what I've done I've
trabaja más allá de lo que he hecho he
made three videos get interested or I'm going to
hecho tres vídeos interesarse o voy a
be direct here I've already fulfilled family has
ser directo aquí ya he cumplido familia
fulfilled his name is that it is a
haya cumplido su nombre es que es un
video that I have to see it carefully and I don't have
vídeo que tengo verlo detenidamente y no
time then I'm going to leave
me da tiempo entonces voy a dejar otros
two more to xeito if I can at night I'll
dos al xeito si puedo por la noche
come back and if not tomorrow okay well
vuelvo y si no pues mañana vale pues
tomorrow I'll show you a video that I want to
mañana os enseño un vídeo que os quiero
show you today I can't become a member
enseñar yo hoy no puedo hacerme miembros
javi what has to be later well
javi que tiene que ser después bueno
danielle okay you can
danielle vale
bro you want
te puedes hermano tú quieras
you can do it whenever you want and if you do
te puedes hacer cuando tú quieras y si
n't want that's okay today
no quieres tampoco pasa nada hoy
self-employment has said several things in
autoempleo ha dicho varias cositas en
his live streams okay and we're going to like those
sus directos vale y nos va a gustar esas
things that he said let's see the
cositas que ha dicho vamos a ver la
gta crowd it really seems like it's a
gta de verdad es que parece que es un
secret when gta you give us a clue what
secreto cuando gta nos das una pista que
clue if I tell you and if I'm
pista si te lo digo y si te estoy
opening my ass and the chasing you
abriendo el culo y que los persigue te
have announced
hayan anunciado
if you have to rest is that if I'm going
si tienes que descansar es que si me voy
to dinner at the beach well I'm not going to come
a cenar a la playa pues no os voy a
back and I'm going to open live I'll be left
volver y voy a abrir directo ya me quedo
with my ass broken I already
con el culo roto
believe I'll stay lazing around all day
ya me creo me quedo vagueando todo día
the morning will be another one I'm giving gta it
la mañana será otra le estoy dando gta
's in April next month and I'm going to be
es en abril el mes que viene y yo voy a
coming it starts now the London
estar que viene empieza ya el london
this then the announced in London
este lo entonces el anunciado en londres
not much I'll warn him a month or two
no mucho yo le advierto un mes o dos
and it's over I'm going to do a mini story
y se acabó voy a hacer una mini historia
that  I have it ready
que tengo preparada
and that's it and I'm going to leave because it's already and
y ya está y me voy a ir porque ya está y
I
yo
officially after London left
oficialmente después de londres dejó el
role play forever
role play for ever
this also I told you already this is
esto ya también te lo dije ya esto es
another thing that I had to clarify with
otra cosa que tenía que aclarar con a
sometimes because I didn't like it right
veces porque yo no le gustase acertado
me the other day well this and when
yo el otro día pues esto y cuando
they announced that I had been meeting and it
anunciaron haber sido encuentro y es que
was a video that I downloaded and I had it
fue un vídeo que lo descargue y lo tenía
on my phone so when the
en el móvil yo para cuando llegue el
right moment comes it
momento adecuado
will be literally I say when I
sea literalmente digo para cuando
find the right moment to see if
encuentre el momento adecuado a ver si
I have the video here to see if it
yo tengo el vídeo aquí a ver si se
plays nice
reproduce bonita
[Music]
[Música]
thanks server that it is totally I do
gracias servidor de que sea totalmente
n't know what this scene is about but it is
no sé de qué será esta escena pero es
literally a GTA server
literalmente un servidor de gta
[Music]
[Música]
totally okay I don't know I don't know what
totalmente vale no sé no sé a qué
the scene belongs to but let's
pertenecen a la escena pero vamos
literally the server okay you're back to
literal el servidor vale ya volviste a
being the live shows on YouTube yes mayor
ser los directos por youtube sí alcalde
what you have to do since I'm
lo que tenéis que hacer ustedes como ya
back is check that you have the
he vuelto es revisar que tenéis las
subscriptions to Billy Vida
suscripciones a billy vida
check that you have the Skilled Hybrid subscription
revisar que tenéis la suscripción hábil
check that you are subscribed to Biel
revisar qué estáis suscritos a biel
Canino and check and this please do
canino y revisar y esto por favor se le
a favor to your mother and our
el favor a vuestra madre ya nuestras
grandmothers subscribe tie them to the CEO man
abuelas suscribiros áteles al ceo hombre
that you have arrived with two plates to the
que habéis llegado con dos placas al
channel to the channels with two plates of
canal a los canales con dos placas de
the 100,000 we are going to reach the
los 100.000 vamos a llegar a la tercera
third plate okay we are going to reach the plate of televisions to the pse or so please do him the favor subscribe to the sauce too that it costs us money damn 6 and that this is another thing that I had to clarify I had reminded you the other day I put see you in London in my final season and
vemos en londres en mi temporada final y
there were people who said something ending without
había gente que decía algo final sin
ending when I finished London I am not going to
final yo cuando acabé londres no voy a
do more role play it's over I leave my
hacer más role play se acabó ya dejo mi
stage suddenly and close that chapter
etapa de golpe y cierro ese capítulo
but I think it's necessary to do
pero es que creo que es necesario hacer
what I have to do to close
lo que tengo que hacer para cerrar
several things and have a good time of
varias cositas y pasarlo bien por
course and laugh and cry and that's it
supuesto y reírnos y llorar y ya está
but after this month or two in
pero después de este mes o dos de
London it's
londres
over I will not do role play again
se acabó yo no vuelva a hacer role play
not in London or anywhere else
ni en londres ni en ninguna otra parte
I will dedicate myself to other things I
yo ya me dedicaré a otras cositas me
really like creating mini events I don't
gusta mucho lo de crear mini eventos no
know why foods I looked at events hopefully it
sé por qué alimentos miré eventos ojalá
sent me at the time allowing hopefully I
me envió a la hora permitiendo ojalá me
hopefully they make another one and I have  the
ojalá hagan otro y tenga yo la
opportunity also the other day
oportunidad también el otro día
they announced some mini events well I don't know
anunciaron unos mini eventos bueno no sé
if in mini events I do
si en mini eventos
n't know if in my event
no sé si en mi evento
[Music]
[Música]
and it doesn't feel like another copy alexandra
y tampoco se siente otra copia alexandra
for seven months and cough
para siete meses y tos
seven months and cough remind you that you have
siete meses y tos recordaros que tenéis
the link fixed I don't know if these mini
fijado el enlace no sé si estos mini
events says
eventos dice
the new skip game ten project
el nuevo proyecto de skip game ten
is cooking from skeet game team
se está cocinando de skeet game team
they will be the same not the blond aurum play
serán los mismos no el rubio aurum play
or
o
and comanche the computer team and
y comanche el equipo de informáticos y
such that was on
tal que había
April 1st there will be more information
el 1 de abril habrá más información
stay tuned because there is still missing
estén atentos pues todavía falta
but well the trailer
pero bueno el tráiler
ah
ah
[Music] let's
[Música]
see the moment they
a ver el momento
tell me they tell me and I can't reveal the
me dicen me dicen y no puedo revelar la
source okay but they tell me
fuente vale pero me dicen
about my event nothing is going to be 50 times
de mi evento nada va a ser 50 veces
better I do
mejor
n't know if they are going to open options for me to
no sé si van a abrir opciones de que
enter we can present something
pueda entrar podemos presentarnos algo
[Music]
[Música]
why
por qué
and
y
[Music] there is
[Música]
behind
hay atrás
well I say god I do
pues ya digo dios
n't know
no lo sé
my whole team and I are we will be
todo mi equipo y yo estamos estaremos
developing a new project with
desarrollando un nuevo proyecto con
aurum play and if they cried trembled and
aurum play y si lloraron temblaron y
suffered with skip craft game of fue put get
sufrieron con skip craft game of fue put
ready to sweat cold
a prepararse para sudar frío
I do know  can I introduce myself
yo si se puede me presento
n't know if automatically the same ones
no sé si automáticamente los mismos
will be there or something
estaremos o algo
or we will have the opportunity I don't know the
o tendremos la oportunidad no lo sé la
truth I don't
verdad
know man
no lo sé tío
how is it that James like what is coming
cómo es que james como lo que se viene
now I am going to dedicate myself to that because it is
ahora me voy a dedicar a eso porque es
what I like I realize what I like I
lo que me gusta me da cuenta de qué es
really like to
lo que me mola me gusta mucho hacer
study creating mini things
estudio crear mini cosas
mini events and such and things it is what I
mini eventos y tal y cosas es lo que me
like it is what I like which is why I
gusta es lo que me gusta por lo cual
think that I am going to dedicate myself to that of
creo que me voy a dedicar a eso por
course I will dedicate myself to tortilla
supuesto que me dedicaré a tortilla
tortilla it will last several months and tortillas
tortilla durará varios meses y tortillas
yes to death with tortilla to death because
sí a muerte con tortilla a muerte porque
I like it more than gta the truth is I like
me gusta más que gta la verdad me gusta
2 a lot more I like
bastante más 2 me gusta bastante más
minecraft a lot more than gta I see it much healthier
minecraft que gta lo veo mucho más sano
fun with many more options
divertido con muchas más opciones
I see it much better I'm sorry but
lo veo mucho mejor lo siento pero es que
in my opinion I like minecraft much more
en mi opinión me gusta mucho más
than gta gta in my opinion is
minecraft que gta gta en mi opinión es
very closed few options
es muy cerrado pocas opciones
or you make ip or so you are going to take it up the ass
o haces ip o so te vas a tomar por culo
and my children I am [ __ ] ashamed to
y a mis hijos me da [__] vergüenza
do it I really refuse to do that [ __ ]
hacerlo de verdad me niego a hacer esa
before doing that [ __ ] I take and
[__] antes de hacer esa [__] cojo y
turn off the stream you will see disgusting I can't with the
apagó stream verán asco no puedo con los
worst me  they are repulsive disgusting vomit
peores me dan repulsión asco vómito
or you do and worse or you are the leader of a gang
o haces y peor o eres jefe de una banda
or is it always the same people like that
o es que siempre lo mismo gente así
fed up with always seeing the same thing or you
hasta la [__] de ver siempre lo mismo o
make a chip eo or for example of a
haces un chip eo o por ejemplo de una
gang or
banda o
is it that if you are a police officer always on the
es que si eres policía siempre en lo
same day
mismo día
always the same and I am not going to fall for
siempre lo mismo y yo no voy a caer en
what everyone does I refuse I am
lo que hace todo el mundo me niego yo
going to do the same story pipe boom
voy a hacer una misma historia pipa boom
and take it up the ass and I leave that world
y a tomar por culo y me voy de ese mundo
that is not my favorite I must say it is not
que no es mi favorito debo decir no es
my favorite apart from gta there are a lot there are a lot a lot of
mi favorito aparte del gta hay mucho
people approach you for interests
se acerca mucha gente por intereses
people I am sorry but I have to say it
gente lo siento pero tengo que decirlo
approaches you and a lot of people
se te acerca y mucha gente
and it pisses me off I like to
y a mí me toca los huevos a mí me gusta
choose who I hang out with I mean I play you go
elegir con quién me junto es decir juego
out with you with you with you and with
salgáis contigo contigo contigo y
you I play minecraft with you with you with you
contigo juego a minecraft contigo
and with you in gta on the
contigo contigo y contigo en gta en
other hand it is very open
cambio es muy abierto se te puede
anyone can approach you and that pisses me
acercar cualquiera y eso me toca los
off because maybe you make a
huevos porque igual haces famoso una
[ __ ] great person famous like is
persona de [__] madre como es
from carche etc etc or you make an idiot that
del carche etc etc o haces a un imbécil
is what pisses me off no yes of course
eso es lo que me jode que no sí claro
but let's see he is there too
pero a ver ahí también está él
how do you see if someone has approached  or it
como se ve si alguien se ha acercado o
has come out organically, I mean when
ha salido orgánicamente o sea cuando
someone comes out organically and hey look listen to
alguien sale orgánicamente y oye mira
me
cucha me
to have the opportunity
a tener la oportunidad
but when someone is forcing the
pero cuando alguien está forzando el
role
roll
kf that man please
kf ese hombre por favor
to fs
a fs
please and now a play what happens is that I did
por favor y ahora un play lo que pasa es
not play calmly
que no jugaba tranquilo
in part yes because he also backs
en parte sí porque también echa para
down there are people who know it but there are
atrás hay gente que lo sabe pero hay
other people who do not there are
otra gente que no hay gente que hay
people that there are people who do not realize that it is noticeable that they are forcing the role well there is a little degree that is a little disgusting but they do not care and say forward forward okay but of course there is the issue that you want that not in the server in the
que quieras que no en el servidor en la
city is
ciudad está
and if the vultures can approach him
y si le pueden acercar los buitres
there are around no I cannot choose almost
hay alrededor no no puedo elegir casi
anything I do not have control and that pisses me off
nada no tengo el control y eso me toca
because you can introduce
los huevos porque puedes dar a conocer a
wonderful people like axon
gente maravillosa como puede ser axón
momon the
momón el
carche revol
carche revol
etc etc who are people who say this I am
etc etc que son gente que dice esto me
glad that it went well for you or blessed
alegra que te haya ido bien o le bendito
be the day look you came to give me a
sea el día mira que viniste a darme una
great gun but the thing is that you
pistola genial pero es que también
can also make an idiot out of an [ __ ]
puedes hacer un imbécil a un [__]
and that is not having total control it
y eso es el no tener el control total me
bothers me it bothers me for  that's what I want to get out
molesta me molesta por eso quiero salir
of those worlds where I don't have
de esos mundos donde yo no tengo el
control, I don't like it, I don't like it, I like to
control no me gusta no me gusta me gusta
have control, to say you, you, you, and
tener el control de decir tú tú tú tú y
you and that's it because I know that you are [ __ ]
tú y ya está porque sé que sois de [__]
great and it will be worth it.
madre y va a valer la pena
The objective channel is that I put this with
el canal objetivo es que pongo esto con
love, it is very complicated,
amor es es muy complicado
something very strong had happened, that my
había pasado algo muy fuerte el que mi
ex-mine, gamer, who has gone through so much
ex mina gamer que ha pasado tan fuerte
if in the end what you have in full mont
si al final lo que tienes en plena mont
for gave him the opportunity to Huaylas, that
por le dio la oportunidad de huaylas ese
acquaintance to whoever you want that
conocido a quien quiera que quieres que
no
no
and if you close yourself off in people something that
y si te cierras en gente algo que
closed r they do nothing they do
cerrado r no hacen nada
nothing but the thing is that I think that I
no hacen nada pero es que yo creo que a
owe the people it is useful I do it for the
la gente le debo es útil lo hago por la
people I do it out of respect for history I
gente lo hago por respeto a la historia
cannot make the stories that I have
no puedo hacer las historias que he
made and leave it like that, the truth is for that, do
hecho y dejarlo así la verdad para eso
nothing, I think that I owe
no hagas nada creo que le debo a la
people
gente
the end, I owe people the end, I
el final le debo a la gente el final le
owe people to relive certain moments
debo a la gente revivir ciertos momentos
and that's it and say goodbye through the
y ya está y despedirnos por la puerta
front door to be able to say, look, now one step
grande poder decir mira ahora un paso
in this world made a [ __ ]
por este mundo hizo una historia de [__]
great story but he left because he doesn't like that, what
madre pero se fue porque no le gusta eso
I want, no more, no less  a
lo que quiero yo ni más ni menos dar un
good ending and go that's what I want a
buen final e irme eso quiero una
farewell I think I owe it above all
despedida creo que se lo debo sobre todo
to the fund oms I understand I understand
a los fund oms lo entiendo lo entiendo
perfectly let's see if you like the place
perfectamente a ver si te gusta el sitio
playing it's not that because of the inconvenience
jugando ya no es que por por molestias
of third parties you're going to deprive yourself of
de gente de terceros vayas a privarse de
doing what I that what's happening I
hacer al que yo que lo que está pasando
already know
ya sé
if I wished I say it now I say it but
si deseara lo digo ahora lo digo pero
something that very well euro there are
algo que muy bien euro
many languages on the planet and today
hay muchos idiomas en el planeta y hoy
they have decided to speak the truth
han decidido hablar con la verdad
I was here of course this has to
estaba yo aquí claro que esto tiene que
do with the second thing that we are going to
ver con la segunda cosa que vamos a
deal with and it is that I was here watching out of the
tratar y es que estaba aquí viendo de
corner of my eye
reojo
from rodelillo
de rodelillo
in tweet
en tweet
that they are banks more than 100,000
que está ellos bancos más de 100.000
viewers I say that you have made friends
espectadores digo que has hecho amigos
that you have made and see down below call of duty of
que has hecho y ver abajo call of duty
course and it's that today there is a movement today there is
claro y es que hoy hay una movida hoy
a willy red movement I do
hay una movida de willy red
n't know why they are there that is
no sé por qué están allí
what I don't know I don't know then
eso es lo que no sé
why is he there I I well
entonces por qué está ahí yo yo bueno
there look
ahí mira
[Music]
[Música]
willis
willis
the ibex
el ibex
tournament
torneo
but I don't know why welcome Jessica
pero no sé por qué bienvenida jessica
thank you very much I don't know why I do
muchísimas gracias no sé por qué
n't know why you are yoga
no sé por qué estáis yoga
and giovan explodes with the return of willy
y giovan explota con la vuelta de willy
kings stacks I know it's a tournament and
reyes stacks sé que es un torneo y
also before willy he had another miniature let's
además ante willy tenía otra miniatura
see if by getting in I can see it
a ver si metiéndome lo consigo ver
before I had another miniature in which
antes tenía otra miniatura en la que
the stack was and I juan and I don't know who
estaba el stack y yo juan y no sé quién
but I think in the group of the
pero que creo que en el grupo de la
kids I have
chavalería tengo
a dry tree
un árbol seco
dry salmon
salmón seco
to who organizes it and
a que lo organiza y
with mmd
con mmd
and
y
bad with thank you very much and juan gave with the
mal con muchas gracias y dio juan con el
kiss
beso
listen to me
escúchame
[Music]
[Música]
has to load I show it
tiene que cargar lo enseño
so one organizes it but like he has
así que la organiza one pero como que ha
invited willy that one that tried has I didn't
invitado a willy esa que trató tiene no
know what he
sabía qué
had in that contact forget there are
que tenía en ese contacto olvida están
the miniatures that I had before it
las miniaturas que yo había antes
says
dice
tournament modern warfare
torneo modern warfare
warfare 3 and it's
warfare 3 y está
[Music] I
[Música]
mean but let's see I don't understand
o sea pero vamos a ver yo no entiendo
one thing here in our miniature
una cosa aquí en nuestra miniatura
you have uploaded a post commenting on the subject
tú has subido un post comentando el tema
in the forum you saw nierob everyone is already
en el foro viste nierob ya está todo el
informed in fact well in my
mundo enterados de hecho bien en mi
kids dotcom right now we are going there
chavalería puntocom ahora mismo vamos
but be it and iowa- invites the blond to
ahí pero sea y iowa- invita al rubio a
stacks and willy and willy gets the
stacks y a willy y willy se pone el
bastard in the miniature with this
cabrón en la miniatura con esta va a
the pse is going to be created or like the story
crearse al pse o como la historia
welcome to  Claudia thank you very much
bienvenida a claudia muchísimas gracias
20 good welcome not at all by Carlos it has
20 buena bienvenida para nada por carlos
been 27 months which is said soon but
lleva 27 meses que se dice pronto pero
that is a lot of seniority
eso mucha antigüedad
more than one would like to have had that
ya quisiera más de un haber tenido esa
seniority in some job
antigüedad en algún trabajo
[Laughs]
[Risas]
Vegeta would be missing and I'm freaking out work see but
faltaría vegeta y flipo obra ver pero
this has created a bit of salsa or the
esto ha creado un poco de salsa o la
miniature a bit tacky I also tell you
miniatura un poco cutre también te digo
this has been done by the state if I dance knitted
esto lo ha hecho el estado si baile
a pompom like the ones
hecho punto un pompón como las que hago
I do in telehealth Serbia Isabel Canino and I
yo en telesalud serbia isabel canino y
make gave a png of Call of Duty
hago dio un png de call of duty
and has been able to and has put these to create
y ha podido y ha puesto estas para crear
salsa
salsero
and cold of your the
y fría de tu
curious thing about the subject was a video
lo curioso del tema fue un vídeo
dukes and thank you very much look at you that the
dukes y muchas gracias fíjate tú que lo
curious thing about the subject what is that look what he
curioso del tema cuál es que mira lo que
said when starting directly do you
ha dicho cuando a empezar directo
think that I believe that Greg this fact was
crees que creo que greg este hecho se
put that he relates macho what a rat the first
puso que relata macho que rata el primer
video that the serious object that uploaded
vídeo que el objeto de grave que subía
videos that nobody saw was a
vídeos que no se lo veía nadie fue un
video insulting Frank enjoy that if
vídeo insultando a frank disfruta que si
the vials saw a thousand people well
los viales veían mil personas pues de
suddenly that is what he chose like
repente eso es lo que escogió como
100,000 not calling him man how I know that I
100.000 no llamándole man como sé que yo
like that  it arrives well then I think he
como que llega bien luego creo que me
made another one to me and after that well it
hizo otro a mí y después de eso pues
started to be a little with the wake or
empezó a ser un poco con con la estela o
crashing it was not wanted that moment okay
chocar no se quería ese momento vale
willy says the rat and
dice willy que la rata y de muchas
thank you very much
gracias
the rat calls him rats okay to believe he
la rata lo llama ratas vale de creer
grew up or rather the first videos that they
creció o sea los primeros vídeos que le
spit out at him were because he started
espetaron fueron porque se puso
enjoying it to them no I was
disfrutarlo a ellos no yo estaba
looking here on greve's channel okay
buscando aquí en el canal de greve vale
for old videos and so what I
por vídeos antiguos y así lo lo que yo
see that there is a video here is that I imagine
veo que hay aquí vídeo es que me imagino
that visits have also been added
que también se habrán añadido visitas
over the years but I see here
durante los años pero veo acá por aquí
the video with 5,000 visits out of 7,000 out of
el vídeo de 5.000 visitas de 7000 de
5,000 it's worth 4 thousand there are some that have
5.000 vale 4 mil hay algunos que tienen
more but of course I imagine that it will be that
más pero claro me imagino que será que
by the title whatever it is the people who
por el título lo que sea la gente que le
follow it have obviously been coming and there
sigue evidentemente ha ido viniendo y
are 200 visits per pilar thank you very much
hay 200 visitas por pilar muchas gracias
and the first thing I find okay is that
y lo primero que encuentro vale es que
here the partner ties him very soon from
aquí le ata el partner muy pronto de
greve in maximina the title although I don't
greve en maximina el título aunque yo no
and the first thing he finds is this
y lo primero que encuentra es esto
with willy the miniature very good
con willy la miniatura muy buenos
guys that as you are I bring
chavales que tal como estáis yo traigo
a new  gameplay I'm telling more than a
un nuevo gameplay cuento más que un
gameplay it's a fragment of an
gameplay es un fragmento de una partida
entire game that I was here playing with some
entera que estaba aquí jugando con unos
friends and you see that I placed it in that king's
amigos y veis que ubicó en el de ese rey
and it's nothing more and nothing less than a
y es nada más y nada menos que un
swarm with that one ere being a
enjambre con el de ese ere siendo
swarm with him it was that he hadn't not taken
enjambre con él es era que no se había
any out there was a
no haya sacado ninguno estaba un
swarm with the dcr willy king intervenes
enjambre con el dcr willy rey interviene
way because in the way that I
manera porque en la forma que me lo
took it out it was really impressive doing
saqué fue realmente impresionante hacer
all the time doing russia intrusions
todo el rato haciendo rusia intrusiones
of course what goes for the enemies in case
claro lo que va por los enemigos por si
someone didn't know all the time
alguien no lo sabía todo el rato
doing take care or rather here you see no surly
haciendo cuide o sea aquí veis no hosco
nail nine years ago how much how much
clavo hace nueve años cuánto cuánto
of his face thank you very much king welcome
de su cara muchas gracias rey bienvenido
how old is he now seriously he will be 20
cuántos años tiene ahora grave tendrá 20
[Music]
[Música]
and here he could be for 15-16
y aquí podría tener por 15-16
surely not
seguramente no
how old is he now he's stopped a
cuántos años tiene ahora está parado una
decade
década
these 2013 colleagues there
estos 2013 colegas
are few times that I point but I mean in
hay pocas veces que apunto pero o sea
a way a quite exaggerated thing it
una forma una cosa bastante exagerada
lasts quite little what the gameplay is
dura bastante poco lo que es el gameplay
but I don't know I loved it like at least here
pero no sé me encantó como lo menos aquí
in this game the truth is that I make
en esta partida la verdad que me hago
a streak of 10 kills with the desert in
una racha de 10 bajas con el desert en
something  like a minute and 22 seconds and
algo así como un minuto y 22 segundos y
the truth is that I find it quite
la verdad que me parece bastante
impressive because all the time just like you
impresionante porque todo el rato así
're seeing here visiting the
como estáis viendo aquí visitando el
hot spot clicking and the truth is
punto caliente haciendo clic y la verdad
that I loved it because lately I'm
que me encantó porque últimamente estoy
playing a
jugando
lot, if not to say almost all, almost
mucho sea por no decir casi todo casi
all the time I play, I play with
todo el tiempo de juego juego juego con
Franco because honestly
el franco porque sinceramente
lately I'm a
últimamente ya como que me aburre un
little bored of the improvement a little, I put the table '
poco la mejora un poco me pongo la mesa'
mc the network w such I don't have any of the
mc la red w tal no tengo de los
diamond submachine guns out of laziness to
subfusiles de diamante por pereza de
take the boys and cut them to make
cogerme las chicos y las corte a hacer
heads, the truth is that I don't know lately
cabezas la verdad que no sé últimamente
as I tell you I'm playing quite a few dsr
como os digo estoy jugando bastantes dsr
to set myself challenges I say come on if I'm
a plantearme retos digo vengan si me
exhausted na cuatris whatever it is that I have
agotado na cuatris lo que sea que
n't done it yet I'm playing
todavía no me lo he hecho estoy jugando
and incredibly I know re but I don't do it for a
e increíblemente se re pero no me hago
joke but you know here that I already took
ni de coña pero sabéis aquí que ya me
out of the orbital venesat and like I
sacado del venesat orbital y como he
said in one minute and 20 seconds one
dicho en un minuto y 20 segundos una
thing the truth is quite
cosa la verdad bastante
quite impressive and I am aware
bastante es impresionante y soy consta
of this that companies and doing all the
de esto que empresas y haciendo todo el
time with him of that ere I have one the
rato con él de ese ere tengo uno la
truth is so impressive doing
verdad es tanto impresionante haciendo
turbo low super low five
turbo bajas súper bajas cinco bajas
quick lows  six quick rabbit kills with that one
rápidas seis bajas rabbit rápidas con el
ere or I can if I can upload it
de ese ere o lo puedo si lo puedo subir
if you want because the one they implement
si queréis porque ese que implementan te
is talking to you with a friend and
está hablando con un amigo y no se desea
your time is not desired and Madryn said and you as I'm
tu rato y decía madryn ya ti como estoy
playing with Franco is that they don't
jugando con el franco es que no me lo
believe me and I well here you see I took out
crean y yo bueno aquí ya veis me sacado
the swarm in no time it failed me it was that I will
el enjambre nada de tiempo me falló fue
say it before the
que lo diré antes de que terminara la
round ended because there were always there that
ronda porque quedaban siempre hay que me
saved my streak because I tend to throw it away
salvó la racha pues tiendo a tirarla
just like when they took me out the
igual que cuando me sacaron en el
moment I saw that I had it I would
momento que veía que la tenía yo la
throw it away and here the same thing happens to me I throw it away and
tiraba y aquí me pasa lo mismo la tiro y
then I think I have 20 seconds left
entonces creo que me quedan 20 segundos
for the round to end and I say
para que se termine la ronda y digo
now I'm really serious nothing kid it's
ahora estoy huevo grave nada chaval está
always very short very short it's already
siempre muy corto muy cortito ya es
Sunday morning
domingo mañana
of
de
[ __ ] nor what is done a 4 from
putada ni que se hace un 4 de hace
four days ago kids
cuatro días chavales
and our willy
y nuestra willy
what
qué
is
es
wow
wow
444 calm down willy guys okay okay
444 tranquilo willy tíos vale vale
and what willy god
y lo willy dios
wow wow act calm willy guys
guau guau actuar tranquilo willy tíos
okay okay
vale vale
but it was hui led until I have done
pero era hui lideró hasta que he hecho
quack quack quack  calm down willy guys okay
cuac cuac cuac tranquilo willy tíos vale
okay I
vale
don't know if it's the real willy or not but
no sé si será el willy real o no pero el
what surprises me is that he was known at all I don't
que me extraña que se conociera algo no
know I think he would be a fan of willy
lo sé yo creo que él sería fan de willy
isn't like that the only thing they found were the
no es así lo único que encontraron los
stamps and he will still have this video
sellos y tendrá todavía el vídeo este
that says the one who has a video where he
que dice el que tiene un vídeo donde
is insulting him first to one and since I have
está insultando le primero a uno y como
gotten a lot of visits the other one I mean I ca
le he cogido mucha visita el otro o sea
n't find it okay but look it
no encuentro vale pero fíjate
's a kid who comes down that's going to throw
es un niño que le baja que le va a echar
in his face a kid probably here didn't
en cara un niño seguramente aquí no se
sleep or can't sleep
tiraba ni puede dormir
for some reason
por algún motivo
when you put farts in the search
cuando pones pedos en la búsqueda te
these three videos appear they exist
aparecen estos tres vídeos existen a
willy but maybe a recording okay
willy pero a lo mejor una grabación vale
and then he said something else willy said
y luego ha dicho algo más willy ha dicho
something else that we're going to see
algo más que lo vamos a ver
election he loves him a lot and you're going to be
elección le quiere mucho y vais a estar
killing greece will
mataba con grecia will
red lan fixing very good
red lan arreglando muy buena
communication
comunicación
[Music] I
[Música]
choose olive tree
elijo al olivo
they don't like
no les cae bien
direction he loves him a lot and vice
dirección le quiere mucho y vice
ours killed greece
nuestras mataba con grecia willy
I like willy and what does greg say is that I think
me cae bien y que dice greg es que creo
what he says my place is right
que lo que dice mi lugar es derecha
valeri who knows what kids in case
valeri a saber qué chavalería por si
someone doesn't know  well our forums
alguien no lo sabe pues nuestros foros
click valeri dot com
pincha valeri a puntocom
our forums from which we can go home to the
nuestros foros del que podemos a casa al
followed we go to forums and what is it that you are
seguido nos vamos a foros y qué es lo
supposed to have posted it
que se supone que has puesto
feels if a woman comes back from the
se siente si vuelve una mujer de las
realities to the top by treating her
realidades a tope con tratarla de manera
lightly will is exposed for this
ligera will es expuesto por esto
for yoga tournament
por torneo de yoga
to for stealing a thumbnail to the thumbnail
a por robar una miniatura a la miniatura
but it was natural while vale
pero es que era natural mientras vale
that was the move with the golden life
esa era la movida con la vida dorada al
apparently willy rey is back in the eye
parecer willy rey vuelva a estar el ojo
of the hurricane on twitter for having taken
del huracán por twitter por haber cogido
an edited photo from a media outlet and since it is
una foto editada de un medio y como se
known that willy has stolen said photo
sabe que willy le ha robado dicha foto
because the same editor of said media outlet
porque el mismo editor de dicho medio lo
has said so on twitter
ha dicho en twitter
willy a lot indeed but well that
willy mucho en efecto pero bien que
the cover photo of a dog is better
mejor sean la foto de portada de perro
but oh well
pero bueno
the photo was accepted as it is
se acogió la foto tal cual es
I was left with the idea that at least he had made
yo me quedé que al menos le había hecho
the one who captures it weak willy what a
el que capte flojo willy que flojo
weak [ __ ] he is to the gods look at the
cabrón sea a los dios fíjate de las
little things as a leader he was in villa
cositas como dirigente era en villa
valeria dot com and it is totally free to
valeria puntocom y es totalmente gratis
register for this motto people
registrarse este lema gente el directo
willy's live show for today's tournament I am happy
de willy para el torneo de hoy soy feliz
thanks elements or for making it possible
gracias elements o por hacerlo posible
today and now they changed it  or today that I
hoy y ahora la cambiaron o hoy a que me
put it on as a thumbnail
la pongo yo de miniatura
nothing nobody
nada nadie
and turn off the screen I don't know what I'm
y apagar la pantalla no sé qué es lo que
doing here it
hago aquí
feels now I have the whole setup
se siente ahora yo tengo todo el setup
in the [ __ ] [ __ ] there's something that
en la putísima [__] hay algo que a
empty in touching the microphone that turned off the
vacía en tocar el micrófono que apagó la
screen
pantalla
like 'the cove' in that
como 'the cove' en eso
now
ahora
how do you eat that moving the microphone cable
como te comes que moviendo el cable del
turn off the screen does not acquire the
apague la pantalla no adquiera la fruta
present fruit since I make friends friends that I have to
presente ya que hago amigos amigos que
cut in back
tengo que cortar en atrás
friend
amigo
now it transcended gave father via
ahora trascendió dio padre vía
my mother I
madre mía
was starting well good family I
me estaba empezando bien bueno familia
have to go
me tengo que ir
and very little time to be able to what very little
y poquísimo tiempo poder que poquísimo
time not even an hour 47 minutes
tiempo ni una hora siquiera 47 minutos
god I have to hours to the dog and me
dios me tengo que horas al perro y me
everything with the way everything traveling
todo con el camino todo viajar
traveling must count many things then there will be
viajar debe contar muchas cosas luego
many powerful
estará muchas cosas
powerful things with tasks
potentes con tareas
lion already thank you very much but lion already you
león ya muchas gracias pero león ya tú
because because every time you donate lion you already
porque porque cada vez que donas león ya
do it
lo haces
with a treat and they don't put anything and I don't go out and
con convite y no ponen nada y no salgo y
behind
detrás
or
o bien
brutal it's brutal today brutal today the beat
brutal es brutal hoy brutal hoy la beat
we have released the archangel gabriel
hemos estrenado el arcángel gabriel
that loses hard
que pierde duro
that the archangel gabriel we had not
que el arcángel gabriel no lo habíamos
released it family I'm sorry I'm
habíamos estrenado familia lo siento lo
sorry that there are  until this weekend
siento que hay hasta este fin de semana
so short because I was busy with other
tan corto porque estaba liado con otras
things that you will find out about, I don't know if
cosas que ya os enteraréis no sé si
there will be a live show, it depends on the time I
habrá directo depende a la hora que
arrive, but I already think that we won't even take it
llegue pero ya creo que ni lo tomaremos
as a break. If I upload something, it's that
de descanso si subo algo es que salga
some people go out to the PSE or more or less well
algunos al pse o más o menos bien
and I
y le
do the news, but I don't
y haga las noticias pero en directo no
think so, live, I don't think so tomorrow, yes, tomorrow we'll see
creo en directo no creo mañana si mañana
them live tomorrow, live from the two
les directo mañana de directo de las dos
kids, Mr. Era,
chavales señor ería
thanks to the people
gracias a gente
[Music]
[Música]